{
    "questions": {
            "questions_1": {
                "1": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países es limítrofe con Rusia?",
                    "answer_1": "Afganistan",
                    "answer_2": "Pakistan",
                    "answer_3": "Letonia",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_3"
                },
                "2": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países tiene el color rojo en su bandera?",
                    "answer_1": "Perú",
                    "answer_2": "Brasil",
                    "answer_3": "Venezuela",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_1"
                }
            },
            "questions_2": {
                "1": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países es limítrofe con Rusia?",
                    "answer_1": "Afganistan",
                    "answer_2": "Pakistan",
                    "answer_3": "Letonia",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_3"
                },
                "2": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países tiene el color rojo en su bandera?",
                    "answer_1": "Perú",
                    "answer_2": "Brasil",
                    "answer_3": "Venezuela",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_1"
                }
            },
            "questions_3": {
                "1": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países es limítrofe con Rusia?",
                    "answer_1": "Afganistan",
                    "answer_2": "Pakistan",
                    "answer_3": "Letonia",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_3"
                },
                "2": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países tiene el color rojo en su bandera?",
                    "answer_1": "Perú",
                    "answer_2": "Brasil",
                    "answer_3": "Venezuela",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_1"
                }
            },
            "questions_4": {
                "1": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países es limítrofe con Rusia?",
                    "answer_1": "Afganistan",
                    "answer_2": "Pakistan",
                    "answer_3": "Letonia",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_3"
                },
                "2": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países tiene el color rojo en su bandera?",
                    "answer_1": "Perú",
                    "answer_2": "Brasil",
                    "answer_3": "Venezuela",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_1"
                }
            },
            "questions_5": {
                "1": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países es limítrofe con Rusia?",
                    "answer_1": "Afganistan",
                    "answer_2": "Pakistan",
                    "answer_3": "Letonia",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_3"
                },
                "2": {
                    "question": "¿Cuál de estos países tiene el color rojo en su bandera?",
                    "answer_1": "Perú",
                    "answer_2": "Brasil",
                    "answer_3": "Venezuela",
                    "correct_answer": "answer_1"
                }
            }
        },
    "users": {
        "MH5Fv0wU6wZvrhOSz8u7dOf9F4v1":{
            "points": 0,
            "answer_1": true,
            "answer_2": false,
            "answer_3": false
        }
    }
}